{
  "LANGHINDI": 18,
  "qu1": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following is an example of indirect cost?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Purchased equipment installation cost",
      "OPT2": "Piping",
      "OPT3": "Supervision cost",
      "OPT4": "Land cost",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu2": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A pump has salvage value of Rs. 40000 and a estimated life of 10 years. Original cost of pump is 500000. If annual interest rate is 10%, book value of pump after 5 years using sinking fund depreciation method will be</p>",
      "OPT1": "Rs. 176210",
      "OPT2": "Rs. 424031",
      "OPT3": "Rs. 493115",
      "OPT4": "Rs. 323790",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu3": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Purchased cost of an equipment of area 20 m2 in 2003 is Rs. 9000. What will be the cost of equipment in year 2015 of area 80 m2?<br />\r\nThe equipment cost versus capacity index is 0.54<br />\r\nMarshall and Swift index are as below:</p>\r\n\r\n<div>\u00a0</div>\r\n\r\n<div><img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAQYAAABNCAYAAABE3conAAARq0lEQVR4Xu1de1BU1x3+TJxMamK0pilB06QTUzRTM62CJBnTCGuxsb4YMNYXj7C10kh8MIDagJNUfAQoipqMxoEAviY2UEQdHC0IzthkVJo0mikwyjQviWOSMUiMY63pOfex3L17d7139+7sucezfzHsPWfP+f2+++05v3P3+wZ8T14QLxEBEQERAU0EBghiEHgQERAR0EdAEIPAhIiAiIBPBAQxCFCICIgIhEYMAwYMECEUERARuEUEeCjbWVoxUGLgYdJORrbIAdvZ4yU/ghjYxpnvEk+QM9MZE8TAdHr4HRwvwOM1Q7zkR6wYHIZQXoDnCfvNHrQfOIh9O/owu2E5Ygc6LCG64fKSHwcRQx/ay6YjLr8ViF6MulPlSBlxl3da+k6ibPqLOJNWjdezxuBeZ2PMcPSRBZ4mB57RLULdha1IibZ+R99oL8PouHycp32NLMXpjjxBDIxg1kHEQCN2HT0t6zFv0itoTSjH6QNLEXvvHUoor6GrKh0JJ+bg1I4UjFD/zUig7RpGZIlBnoV6Q6P0NDryYmGdEjTRuNGOstFxyIcgBrswYkc/DiMGOuVedFQth8t9ElPqDmJHyiOgHHDz83osnNiCqW0GKwk7IsVIHywQA3rqkTE8FSfsJIaRlehsykKMwwmdifzYgFUHEgNlgY9Rv3AaUpsmKluKXrSsmI/dT77pIQobYsNkF0wALxzEMKEOF2pSEM1k1M0Pion8mB+u3yudSQy4ib72CkyPKwVK67En8V1kvvEIqnRbiJs97WjYvRk5+bXoISGITt+Khg0LER9NaxO96Gp5B5VrClHSSt+djILqNViWFo9o+q3V14WWw42oqb6BmZm92PL8enQWNKPjNRfusyHwwXbBBPB8iIFs8dqPoGlfJdpGLcTMzgqklhwhUxyD9NIyvJydhBh1y0eLjQ27sTknH7Uk7NHz0pF4rBZ7kjTEoLuGJA7lDRuwNJ7QRs8JVKxcisYn3sCBvHi5jiTVlpKR//DWiJMLE/kJFlyadg4lBjqDy6QYuYAUIw+Rv59HZWctsmLu9kxN2lqMz0F3Zg32FCch+upZVC2eC/cnWVJt4hcEvM//awrqskaTrYja17dk23wAy7CtvyiGqeR/tchGDeYcexYNoe6pQ0waE8DzIoYfozEjEam1Ugmxn3yjLqGlMAuT1n+FgubDeM31I+UGnodD8SXYXpSMmEEX0b5zE/IyS9CarhCDuhrsnoXmPavgir6mbB0vIvd0FebjJCGgLXCXXECWtJUcgvfLXkDepTS5T0/NKcRAB9mcifwEOXZtMwcTA9lRdFVhyig3jqig8sxMLkSOcg/TVMxvkK1xDoanfq2QyF1kUXAcR85eQPf+9civPUtaj0R63THUpPyEdN6BqikuuM/nMlUtZwJ4PiuGm+htKcToSfuQpMaPRFMuUm7DBOl/Dyg5gTeJq8VHZSsRJeV0HR7U9CPXNHLwRWULmiiRe7aS47B+yUAc652Dakr+DNQnmMjP7U4MBHlyRdtnf2p0rKZGK4GsAOow9+PVGJ9aj1EFr+Kl30yEa0gj4jwgJsSAT1FPvwlPZAti0APNoMbgTQI0fnpi+AGpAz2HSXVzvOOpy+ED2iNM3eeO1BY71e1DZyaaO4rhuo8BViDjFcRgAyuF3IVfYlBXDLpvJ/UD1dUAij2VcF9gC2Lwm5+giOGHynMoD5hYMRSSxCmrA8NB0JOpAiz96B48uHcvPlG3iwxwgyCGkO9qGzpQAFrrs5VQji/Hp6Ipqb/gSIuRB04C8VPvQdNUsk24ni/VG8ZeeZcUtLKRW/td/1aC0fN1FoCnPsdw1VOMDbSVKMdI6SaPwVWpYJyLTrUIHPUVTlasRHIuKQ5PVo4roZ44jfMUHO+Qno58nyTu14hV2sw7OxNtO6bhjlb6XMs7eLhyLxMPtbGQHxvuLDi0xqDWC7ZrYqB/Ao+cXHQdxba1eUr9IBoJBcUocs+CixQpPQ9K0cp5+TYUT3gXiU8qT+H5RJZuPw4gLzbyz1JGFniBtmiaoElEPQOQajpKjqT/TQNO7sDK5BzpRAIJr6C59tf4Z+IzyJdql0qcR13A0W1rkaGcJpHEobLIjdmu4eiUnn7VrjrU51o+Q5r2VMmOuyOIPiKbnyAG7KeJQ4nBvgA4rSdegOe0uJsdLy/5EcRgNuOMXMcL8BgJp+3D4CU/ghhsh0Z4O+QFeOGNUuR65yU/ghgih6GgPpkX4AU1eQc04iU/ghgcADbtEHkBnsPCbnq4vORHEIPplLNxIS/AYyOa9o+Cl/wIYrAfG2HtkRfghTVIEeycl/wIYoggiIL5aF6AF8zcndCGl/xYJgYnJEeMUUQgkhHgwWLBMjHwMOlIgibUz+blGynUOLDanpf8CGJgFWF+xsUL8BwWdtPD5SU/ghhMp5yNC3kBHhvRtH8UvORHEIP92Ahrj7wAL6xBimDnvOTHgcRAtBqPVmJtRq78Cz0jXUGi16j9dV50ejlqXnYjKUZRawz4vr5/nRZkBEFHP5od4Ol/vUpl3bRxNvp162soW/Y7xEqam+SlywPVdiyteRnZSTG38ARRNCbr/oGvx03GjOeejbikmwoLdvITGlAdRwySnNuiT7FC0gMk2qCKz0RnVp3sJ6H8nj/nRh5aXk9DzJVmFM7LABFvk30oBhEBFqIw7e/9sReqMWPtd1hNRWM9uoWqvqAsVR/JFzPAk8Ru8nBuxXYUu0aQRByV49yZIit3R3ejakYpvlldTERc78dFP3lK7Z6Ouu0rkfLYt4o2w0dIUzUijQLd14H6Naux/8Gl2LB0AhNybtphMpOfEEHqMGKggiBrsPxyFiqpLqP0+lKWDCuJk/Qdk6/UEs3AN/BLD7hUEZEjEuDWP9QY4P2DWHZ5IzYNzZfFS8lL1ZU8b4eHQojJYmrF0NuCFcsvY1mlKvmuE2t5+hTcm4Zio6qq7aWhmYufHacakdV4QqvURPscPQklT/jxmJC0HlOx5XGNQrQNMbWzC0EMdkYzpL5U8ZBRhBjKMIaYlhB9WC/5sP6b+zgah23Bz/2+7+usJLetR9LpXUSoZWhII7WjMcvAM9J99MxZIoZp2Jm0h8i+j8MVScSlUyeAE0hO7zo+r8/F+Jz7sIshjUd9TlnOjxX8OWzFYDQ1ZcXwwYtEv3E2rpRThR9KEho/RY9GYTN2YQ2e9vu+jhj6qOT8n3EuY6O0XI70NoKpFYNPKtQVwzkU66T8ZfcwotF4LlVRc+73BblLu2IIpMytvFc4phhvPdSGF6gcHLGnSSjQ1S2soD8M1wpiCENQg+lS9o+owuMH6Df6QEVwNERiUAF6RKpukhc7BUhmgWe4zFdFef+qxFFzI0f1yG5iao0hBuiq34BFqevRamBw67EKSFgl1yRoIVlRii6P3xVxIyAVu8zmx+LN5ewVgwTGTOyfsEURAtVuK2xYMdBgSsWupcRZ6QwmB1Quthj5IC9nE3jyMn/i/vE4SAq+ow1NX8hpj3rjK8Kvj12krlJUhJd4ehBdx+o/jcKHGW7sTfN1/JK3KaqwLDUJoi9l63F0NjMS8mzmxzrYHEwM1D1qMTYPW6VRB1aJwVuiXP62oSYmjVjSvVgnJqoWGHUmJ5pYslSAZA948rYgdfMwVPglBSWYAU181K3Ih8RxyreeY1y/EMRg/ZY318KhxED3rKuJcfrvUZE1RnPm7X0CIZ8saPe+1Zj1WTGphssnFL7v/wU/rd4NrCzwMjCRQdmKbAYKkGwRAyGFjp1YSixE8yu0KwUa8xJsIPlZp5zuSHCUJPmn41B2Q7/vpIpTaVvwIs6kVRvLwCsnFju1qwm17vDQVvmomoEiEFv5MUcCRlc5jxiIx8DJikIU/Y/IxaumptqZqQ5FWCR7Hw7ukjwrCwe+KoPnqmKAavj+b/FtdToS2iZ6zG9vSiaqhfhgorpdCT7YdrRkB3jkISMqBV90HUvqyPMhuu2DtMpKaMNzihkt9YagHhLzPnD5bDeMY6w3DbqmeJX+F6uaq0gxeDCxvFsOl5t6WrJxYkTzy05+QkObw4hBa2RrMHHFeCZKupmVvavBk5EyEI3fv6k+qCM5YNOn+Uqxdcl8JMdGi1MJT8jVU4VctBrij5D2Z6sw9PU/EFNb6notBRKlW5dgfnKs8lASfTLyOA43voMm/ArzZ0whfh9aH3EDNzFqPKOa4Epd6p5oDe1esKW1IAZbwig6sRoBXoBndd5OuZ6X/DhsxeAUeIRvnLwAL3wRimzPvORHEENkcWT503kBnuWJO6QBL/kRxOAQwKnD5AV4Dgu76eHykh9BDKZTzsaFvACPjWjaPwpe8iOIwX5shLVHXoAX1iBFsHNe8iOIIYIgCuajeQFeMHN3Qhte8iOIwQlo04yRF+A5LOymh8tLfiwTg+kIiQtFBG7TCPBgsWCZGHiYtJPxyss3kpNzEGjsvORHEIPDEMoL8BwWdtPD5SU/ghhMp5yNC3kBHhvRtH8UvORHEIP92Ahrj7wAL6xBimDnvOTHgcRgg68EBQ7xNGg53IiaJecws12j9iRpBsQh/7wOXQZyY5HAH0vAk3Uq8uEbKqqdORbXuo5i29o85FOFJvLy/2tIsz4RutyTX2yWqz/rjkQyDD6TpfyEEhLHEUNovhJ/xPDOv6Np3xYUfjEGcz/Zi/LOTG9ZMEoMY+sw7kSxl1hLKEG2sy1LwKPEMHbfOJxQJeK1E72V78QI1XTGrE+EIriz4HPkS2QQhatEJGbxtFOY2UZ8LNT+7Ax2EH2xlJ8ghu9p4jBiCNVXYj+WDTmLfw9+mvz2/xvUZyQi9UQ2TnfkgejIyi9KDE8dQ+J7mv+FEmGb27IEPEoMTx1LxHt5sVDD55nurXwnqC+IJZ8IRbbvzEu4UKN6WcgK4QtQIsRg7cYZOX783myfLIGyf8xWfCW08vB+PAwEMZiFA+HQAMRg0Iu3bmOURZ8IRbilcDAqWzYiazQRdZFWJavw9bq3mPD8oFNm8x4xnVKnrhiMJmjFV8IkMYwtx6XJX6KkXFEfogrGZcuQxoCKE0vAk7YSm3swmW7JJMWrQD4POt+Jx/5DbmoXrPhE9Ktr3Y/00gJMJC5kdybOYSIvKjJZyo91Ouhv4bCthO9UrflKmCSG5Do8Wk69C+4lNcoGrFmUg5LWZ7zcrUIJeihtWQLejfaNSN73CMqLkompbJ+PPHyMVpxVt20YJCl3u3HEkk+ErDNZuL0bQ7spGVHVeWE4Ewqe/LV1NjFY9pUwQQw+kVK/6XQ+i+HIhok+WSIG3+GqPqKP6kjU13fCuk+E0schF9okRWh6kvE2NuWtIBUGxbDY0M/CRFBtvITt/JifqIOJIRhfiWOo8ZjhBvJJ9A6gMYjNB9nOK9kGnpGvh7HvhGWfCOkYeREuvanK/tOoBrLFszPq5vtiOz8W5uHM4mOwvhK1yIq5W4mOETGQb7yyv2FItlsjh84W+JgBXm8ryioHIXt5vMbXQ1vvyULMHf58J0gKrPpESLYAy3GpaL/HidxDDAvAjNEtM/kxzwGGVzpvxRCqr4S671Vdkc5on2Ogy9UCZJ2eqpivqsvVt3Fn0XYmjG2ZAZ60jSNL+PmK4a8q7V49CEXUzyMaAX0nANUKwL9PhOwAVkisy1vQlBWDq8TxanreJbwkeVeq9Z91+MKfSU2IN0cwzZnJTzCD17RxGDHY4SuhrBRqdc/rqU82XqMO13Phlp7Wo1X2YhS5Z+k8D0KMegjN2QGevBpY7MpErWTBQYx/K1fAPTuBFCLJg6X0Jo4L4DtB3cijLgX0ifAmBupXqXvykZwWVRa5MdsVo1m1hBBcG5qyk5/QJuMwYghtsjy05gV4POTCaA685EcQg8MQygvwHBZ208PlJT+CGEynnI0LeQEeG9G0fxS85EcQg/3YCGuPvAAvrEGKYOe85EcQQwRBFMxH8wK8YObuhDa85EcQgxPQpj1GGjAAFn735rDZOX+4ghicn0NHzoAX4Dky+CYGzUt+LK8YTMRGXCIicFtHgIcVnSViuK2zLSYvInAbReD/kU+xzoa5kXoAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" /></div>",
      "OPT1": "Rs. 19788",
      "OPT2": "Rs. 19026",
      "OPT3": "Rs. 41832",
      "OPT4": "Rs. 50123",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu4": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Rs. 100000 can be borrowed from a loan agency at a monthly interest rate of 3%. What will be the effective interest rate when interest is compounded continuously?</p>",
      "OPT1": "23.32%",
      "OPT2": "43.33%",
      "OPT3": "31%",
      "OPT4": "15.26%",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu5": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The total amount to which Rs. 5000 of initial principal would accumulation after 3 years with daily compounding (nominal interest rate is 20%) is</p>",
      "OPT1": "Rs. 8000",
      "OPT2": "Rs. 10560",
      "OPT3": "Rs. 6570",
      "OPT4": "Rs. 9109",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu6": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A plant has estimated salvage value of 3 lakhs in service life of 10 years. If plant has initial worth of Rs. 60 lakhs. The book value of plant after 5 years (in lakhs) is ________. Using decline balance method of depreciation. (Rounded upto second place after decimal)</p>",
      "OPT1": "13.41",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "K5ydErK+SP292+zwapgbrQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu7": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>A heat exchanger has initial cost of Rs. 15000 and a useful life of 10 years salvage value of heat exchanger is 5000. The declining balance depreciation factor which will give same book value at the end of four years as does the straight line depreciation is ________. (Rounded off to third place after decimal)</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.075",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "2pDM1CKCoeo6Ri2V01bp7g==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu8": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>In a chemical plant depreciation on an experiment has been charged on straight line basis using service life of 8 years with salvage value of Rs. 1000. Annual revenue is Rs. 18000 and annual cash expense is Rs. 5800.<br />\r\nIf equipment has initial cost of Rs. 50000, net profit obtained from equipment (assuming tax rate = 25%) (in Rs.) is ________. (Rounded off to nearest integer)</p>",
      "OPT1": "4556.25",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "UIZu/S4wkJ99JEfum1cG2g==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu9": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following cost is/are related to manufacturing fixed capital investment?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Site preparation",
      "OPT2": "Land",
      "OPT3": "Taxes payable",
      "OPT4": "Insulation",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fUwGNpwrpUE3GIKhfsyzGA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fUwGNpwrpUE3GIKhfsyzGA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu10": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>An equipment has original cost of Rs. 50000 and a salvage value of Rs. 2000. This equipment has depreciation allowances of Rs. 5000 during its 2<sup>nd</sup> year of service while depreciated by sum of<br />\r\nyear digit method.<br />\r\nThe recovery period of equipment is</p>",
      "OPT1": "17.1 years",
      "OPT2": "12.6 years",
      "OPT3": "19.2 years",
      "OPT4": "13.8 years",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu11": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>In a chemical plant depreciation cost is estimated to 15% of fixed cost and fixed cost is estimated to be 80% of total investment cost. If rate of return is 20%, the payback period is</p>",
      "OPT1": "4 years",
      "OPT2": "1.5 years",
      "OPT3": "3 years",
      "OPT4": "2.5 years",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu12": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Consider the following statements:<br />\r\n<strong>Statement-I:</strong> In general, the cash flows for the early years of operation are larger than those for<br />\r\nlater years due to effect of depreciation allowance.<br />\r\n<strong>Statement-II:</strong> Usually the revenue for first year after start-up is less than in subsequent years.<br />\r\nWhich of the following options is correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Only statement-I is true",
      "OPT2": "Only statement-II is true",
      "OPT3": "Both the statements are true",
      "OPT4": "Both the statements are false",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu13": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following is not the component of indirect cost of fixed capital investment?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Construction cost",
      "OPT2": "Contractors fees",
      "OPT3": "Contingency",
      "OPT4": "Service facilities",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Wkw/v0ACIC+JhZVbmq0HcA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu14": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Fixed capital investment of a sugar plant is Rs. 1500000. Working capital of plant is 10% of total investment and annual depreciation is 15% of fixed capital investment if annual profit is Rs. 200000.<br />\r\nThen percent rate of return is ________. (Rounded off to first decimal place)</p>",
      "OPT1": "12",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Hfoy3B8dvIY01kI1wBEknA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu15": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The initial cost of a completely installed reactor is Rs. 50000 and salvage value at end of useful life is Rs. 5000.<br />\r\nExcluding depreciation cost for reactor. The total annual expenses for plant is Rs. 200000. 13% of total annual expenses (including depreciation) for plant are due to cost for annual straight line depreciation. Useful life of reactor (in years) is ________. (Rounded upto first decimal place)</p>",
      "OPT1": "1.505",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "ttk1wezM9mX1LHFGF1dqCA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu16": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>The delivered cost of equipments of a fluid processing plant is Rs. 9 \u00d7 10<sup>8</sup>. Using lang factor working capital investment of plant is Rs. ________ \u00d7 10<sup>8</sup> (Rounded off to first decimal place).</p>",
      "OPT1": "8.1",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "vh1/W8ky+albNeQn9VNGxA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu17": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>Which of the following statement/statements is/are incorrect?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Payback period is the length of time over which earnings on a project equals the investment.",
      "OPT2": "Profitability measure \u201creturn on investment\u201d considers time value of money.",
      "OPT3": "Depreciation of a piece of equipment refers to the loss in value with time due to wear, corrosion etc.",
      "OPT4": "Payback period is calculated based on the payback time for the sum of fixed and working capital investment.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "FmRvKjp3/vu5OHwE2HB2FQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "FmRvKjp3/vu5OHwE2HB2FQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13297537",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18434592",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "TEST_NAME": "Topicwise Test-13 Part Syllabus GATE 2026 CH Plant Design and Economics-1",
  "TEST_ID_ENCODED": "NjQzNDE0MQ==",
  "TEST_ID": "NjQzNDE0MQ=="
}